Open Menu Close Menu

Open Menu Close Menu

Last updated February 27, 2023.  

This Single Digits Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains how Single Digits, Inc. and our subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively “Single Digits”, “we,” “us,” or “our”) collect, use and share your personal information. This Privacy Policy applies when you use and interact with our website, singledigits.com, (the “Site”), other websites or digital properties that link to this Privacy Policy, place orders, communicate with our support personnel, marketing or sales representatives, or other employees, attend tradeshows or other events where our marketing representatives or other employees and agents are present, or when you otherwise communicate or connect with us (online, including through social media and third parties, by phone, in-person, or otherwise) (collectively the “Service”).  

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By using the Service, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy and consent to Single Digits’ collection, use and disclosure of personal information and other information as set forth herein. **If you do not consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Service in any way and should immediately exit the Site.**  

* #### Personal information we collect
    
    Collection of Information: We obtain personal information and other information about you from a variety of sources. This includes personal information you provide to us, information we gather through automated means, and information we obtain from other sources.
    
    Information you provide to us. Personal information you may provide to us through the Service or otherwise includes:
    
    Contact data, such as your first and last name, email and mailing addresses, residence and physical address, postal code, phone number, professional title, and organizational affiliation, login id and password.
    
    Payment information including credit card and debit card information.
    
    Communications that we exchange, including when you contact us with questions, feedback, or otherwise.
    
    Marketing data, such as your preferences for receiving communications about our products, services, activities, events, and publications, and details about how you engage with our communications.
    
    Other information that we may collect which is not specifically listed here, which we will use as described in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise disclosed at the time of collection.
    
    Automatic data collection. By choosing to use the Service, you agree to provide Single Digits with certain information that is automatically created, collected, and recorded by your use of the Service Single Digits uses third parties, including Google and Salesforce, to collect this information. Single Digits and these third parties may use a variety of technologies to collect this data, including cookies, JavaScript and logging.
    
    Cookies are text files that websites store on a visitor‘s device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser for the purpose of helping you navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, enabling functionality, helping us understand user activity and patterns, and facilitating online advertising.
    
    The data collected may include but is not limited to your device type and settings, software used, browser type and version, operating system, device id, IP address, Internet service provider, whether you are a new or return user, Web pages you view and time spent on them, links you click on, and what search queries you run on the Service, Websites or other referring services you visited before and after visiting the Service, dates and times you access or use the Service, time zone and location information
    
    Information Obtained from Other Sources: We may obtain personal information and other information about you, in connection with the Service, from publicly and commercially available sources, referrals from others, and from our business partners (such as service providers, social networking services, third-party marketing partners, internet service providers, and data analytics providers) including:
    
    If you interact with us through a third-party (e.g., Facebook, Google, LinkedIn), in addition to the information that you provide, we may obtain information about you, such as your user ID and/or username and other information you have permitted those services to share with us consistent with your privacy settings for that third-party account.
    
* #### How we use your personal information
    
    Single Digits, or service providers acting on our behalf may use your personal information and other information for the following purposes or as otherwise described at the time we collect it:
    
    Service delivery. We use your personal information to:
    
    provide, operate, and improve our products and services,
    
    provide customer service and support;
    
    respond to your inquiries and requests and otherwise communication with you;
    
    provide you with information related to our services or that we otherwise believe will be of interest to you;
    
    notify you about certain changes to the Service;
    
    monitor use of and help us understand how people use the Service;
    
    create and manage online accounts; and
    
    understand your needs and interests, and personalize your experience with the Service and our communications.
    
    Research and development. We may use your personal information for research and development purposes, including to analyze and improve the Service and our business. As part of these activities, we may create aggregated, de-identified or other anonymous data from personal information we collect. We make personal information into anonymous data by removing information that makes the data personally identifiable to you. We may use this anonymous data and share it with third parties for our lawful business purposes, including to analyze and improve the Service and promote our business.
    
    Marketing and advertising. We and our third-party advertising partners may collect and use your personal information for marketing and advertising purposes:
    
    Direct marketing. We may send you Single Digits-related or other direct marketing communications as permitted by law. If you provide us with your email address, you authorize us to send you regular emails unless and until you request to unsubscribe from such emails. These emails may include messages related to your inquiries and requests, marketing communications, and information about changes to the Site. We may collect information about your interactions with emails sent by us or on our behalf, including whether you opened the email or clicked on any links. We may use this information to improve our marketing, to understand our audience, and to improve the Services.  Each email we send contains an automated way for you to unsubscribe from further emails from us.
    
    Interest-based advertising. We may contract with third-party advertising companies and social media companies to display ads on our Service and other sites. These companies may use cookies and similar technologies to collect information about you (including the device data, online activity data and/or geolocation data described above) over time across our Service and other sites and services or your interaction with our emails, and use that information to serve ads that they think will interest you. You can learn more about your choices for limiting interest-based advertising, in the Your Choices section below.
    
    Compliance and protection. We may use your personal information to:
    
    comply with applicable laws, lawful requests, and legal process, such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from government authorities;
    
    protect our, your or others’ rights, privacy, safety or property (including by making and defending legal claims);
    
    audit our internal processes for compliance with legal and contractual requirements and internal policies;
    
    enforce the terms and conditions that govern the Service; and
    
    prevent, identify, investigate and deter fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized, unethical or illegal activity, including cyberattacks and identity theft.
    
* #### How we share your personal information
    
    We do not sell our users’ private personal information. We only share information about you in the situations below, keeping appropriate privacy rules in place:
    
    **Legal Requests:** We may disclose information about you in response to a subpoena, court order, or other governmental request.
    
    **Business Transfers**: In connection with any merger, sale of company assets, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company, or in the unlikely event that Single Digits, Inc. goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would likely be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. If any of these events were to happen, this Privacy Policy would continue to apply to your information and the party receiving your information may continue to use your information, but only consistent with this Privacy Policy.
    
    **Third Party Vendors:** We may share information about you with third party vendors who need to know information about you to provide their services to us, or to provide their services to you. This group includes vendors that help us provide our Services to you (including payment providers that process your credit and debit card information).
    
* #### Your choices
    
    You have the following choices with respect to your personal information.
    
    Opt-out of marketing communications. You may opt out of marketing-related emails by following the opt-out or unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of the email. You may continue to receive service-related and other non-marketing emails.
    
    Automatic data collection. By choosing to use the Service, you agree to provide Single Digits with certain information that is automatically created, collected, and recorded by your use of the Service. Single Digits uses third parties, including Google and Salesforce, to collect this information. Single Digits and these third parties may use a variety of technologies to collect this data, including cookies, JavaScript and logging.
    
    The data collected may include but is not limited to your device type, browser type and version, operating system, device id, IP address, and whether you are a new or return user.
    
    If you interact with us through a third-party (e.g., Facebook, Google, LinkedIn), in addition to the information that you provide, we may obtain information about you, such as your user ID and/or username and other information you have permitted those services to share with us consistent with your **privacy** settings for that third-party account.
    
    Google Ads. We use a number of Google services to assist us with advertising. 
    
    Learn more about Google's practices with regard to data collection and to manage Google Ads.
    
    Social Media and Other Opt-Outs. You can also opt-out of some of our advertising and social media partners by visiting their opt-out pages.
    
    Interest-based advertising. Some of our advertising partners are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) and are subject to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising published by the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA). You can obtain more information about these companies' information collection practices and opt-out of receiving interest-based advertising from participating NAI and DAA members at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp Mobile app users may opt out of receiving interest-based advertising in mobile apps provided by participating members of the Digital Advertising Alliance by installing the AppChoices mobile app, available at https://www.youradchoices.com/appchoices. If you opt-out of interest-based advertisements, you will still see advertisements online, but they may be less relevant to you.
    
    Do Not Track. Some Internet browsers may be configured to send “Do Not Track” signals to the online services that you visit. We currently do not respond to “Do Not Track” or similar signals.
    
    Declining to provide information. We need to collect personal information to provide certain services. If you do not provide the information requested, we may not be able to provide those services.
    
* #### Other sites and services
    
    The Service may contain links to websites, mobile applications, and other online services operated by third parties. These links are not an endorsement of, or representation that we are affiliated with, any third party. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to third party websites, mobile applications, or online services to which the Site links. Single Digits is not responsible for the practices and policies (including privacy policies) of third parties and, therefore, you should review the privacy practices and policies of such third parties prior to providing your personal information in connection with such websites, mobile applications, or online services. In addition, our content may be included on web pages or in mobile applications or other online services that are not associated with us.
    
* #### Security
    
    Single Digits uses reasonable care to protect the privacy and security of personal information and to ensure that our systems are secure and meet industry standards. Unfortunately, no Internet transmission is ever completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss or other breaches will never occur. WE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ANY REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, WITH RESPECT TO ANY BREACHES OF SECURITY, DAMAGE TO YOUR DEVICE, OR ANY LOSS OR UNAUTHORIZED USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION OR OTHER DATA.
    
* #### International data transfer
    
    We are headquartered in the United States and may use service providers that operate in other countries. Your personal information may be transferred to the United States or other locations where privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your state, province, or country. If you choose to use the Service, then please note that you are transferring your personal information outside of your state, province and/or country for storage and processing, and by providing your personal information on the Service you freely and specifically consent to that transfer, storage, and processing.
    
* #### Children
    
    The Service is not intended for use by children under 13 years of age. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under 13 without the consent of the child’s parent or guardian as required by law, we will delete it.
    
* #### Changes to this Privacy Policy
    
    We may periodically revise this Privacy Policy at any time, by posting an amended Privacy Policy on the Site. Your continued use of the Service after any revisions means you consent to and accept the revised Privacy Policy.
    
* #### How to contact us
    
    You can reach us in the following ways:
    
    Email: DPO@singledigits.com
    
    Mail: Single Digits, Inc., 4 Bedford Farms, Suite 210, Bedford, NH, USA 03110
    
* #### Important information for California residents
    
    Scope. This section applies only to California residents. It describes how we collect, use and share Personal Information of California residents when we act as a “business” as defined under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”), and their rights with respect to their Personal Information. This section does not apply when we act as a “service provider” as defined under the CCPA, such as when we process personal information in connection with providing services to our business clients (including when we obtain personal information through our website on the “Support” page or during calls to our support phone numbers). For purposes of this section, “Personal Information” has the meaning given in the CCPA but does not include information exempted from the scope of the CCPA or information we collect from you in the course of providing services to you or receiving services from you where you are an employee, controlling owner, director, officer or contractor of a company, partnership, sole proprietorship, non-profit or government agency. In some cases, we may provide a different privacy notice to certain categories of California residents, such as job applicants, in which case that notice will apply instead of this section.
    
    Your California privacy rights. As a California resident, you have the rights listed below. However, these rights are not absolute, and in certain cases we may decline your request as permitted by law.
    
    Information. You can request the following information about how we have collected and used your Personal Information during the past 12 months:
    
    The categories of Personal Information that we have collected.
    
    The categories of sources from which we collected Personal Information.
    
    The business or commercial purpose for collecting and/or selling Personal Information.
    
    The categories of third parties with whom we share Personal Information.
    
    Whether we have disclosed your Personal Information for a business purpose, and if so, the categories of Personal Information disclosed to each category of third-party recipient.
    
    Whether we’ve sold your Personal Information, and if so, the categories of Personal Information received by each category of third-party recipient.
    
    Access. You can request a copy of the Personal Information that we have collected about you during the past 12 months.
    
    Correction. You can ask us to correct inaccurate Personal Information that we have maintain about you.
    
    Deletion. You can ask us to delete the Personal Information that we have collected from you.
    
    Opt-out of sales. If we sell your Personal Information, you can opt-out. In addition, if you direct us not to sell your Personal Information, we will consider it a request pursuant to California’s “Shine the Light” law to stop sharing your personal information covered by that law with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.
    
    Opt-in. If we know that you are younger than 16 years old, we will ask for your permission (or if you are younger than 13 years old, your parent’s or guardian’s permission) to sell your Personal Information before we do so.
    
    Nondiscrimination. You are entitled to exercise the rights described above free from discrimination in the form of legally prohibited increases in the price or decreases in the quality of our Service.
    
    You may also have the right to appeal the denial of any of these rights by submitting a form that will be provided to you if we deny a data request.
    
    How to exercise your rights
    
    You may exercise your California privacy rights described above as follows:
    
    Right to information, access and deletion. You may exercise your right to information, access or deletion by:
    
    visiting
    
    calling us toll free at
    
    emailing DPO@singledigits.com
    
    Right to opt-out of the “sale” of your Personal Information. Like many companies, we use services that help deliver interest-based ads to you. Our use of some of these services may be classified under California law as a “sale” of your Personal Information to the companies that provide the services because they collect information from our users (e.g., device data and online activity data) to help them serve ads more likely to interest you. You may request that we not use your personal data with these
    
    Advertising Partners by:
    
    visiting or calling us toll free at emailing DPO@singledigits.com
    
    We reserve the right to confirm your California residency to process your requests and will need to confirm your identity to process your requests to exercise your information, access or deletion rights. Government identification may be required. You may designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf. In order to designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf, you must provide a valid power of attorney, the requester’s valid government-issued identification, and the authorized agent’s valid government issued identification. We cannot process your request if you do not provide us with enough detail to allow us to understand and respond to it.
    
    Personal information that we collect, use and disclose
    
    The chart below describes the Personal Information we collect by reference to the categories specified in the CCPA and describes our practices during the 12 months preceding the effective date of this Privacy Policy. Information you voluntarily provide to us, such as in free form webforms, may contain other categories of personal information not described below. Each category is used for the business/commercial purposes described in the section above entitled How we use your personal information, and disclosed to the categories of third parties described in the section above entitled How we share your personal information. We do not collect or process Sensitive Personal Information (as defined by California law) for the purpose of inferring characteristics about individuals.

PRIVACY POLICY
==============

#### **INDUSTRY SOLUTIONS:**

**©2024 SINGLE DIGITS**

**ALL RIGHTS RESERVED**
